Noël-Marie Karvoski

44 Tolland Avenue, Unit 24 ♦ Stafford Springs, CT 06076 ♦ (860) 841-5521 ♦ noelmarie17@hotmail.com

Profile

Motivated, personable professional with a talent for quickly mastering technology. Diplomatic and tactful with professionals and non-professionals at all levels. Hard working, self motivated quick learner adept at managing multiple tasks with accuracy.

Flexible and versatile – able to maintain a sense of humor under pressure. Excellent team-building skills.

Advanced proficiency in numerous software programs including Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, JDE Address Book, JDE Payroll Services, Growth Power and Adobe

Skills Summary

- ♦ Planning
- ◆ Report Preparation
- ◆ Written Correspondence
- ◆ General Office Skills
- ♦ Computer Savvy
- ◆ Purchasing
- ◆ Scheduling
- ◆ Marketing & Sales
- ♦ Aerospace Expediting
- ◆ Legal Secretarial Experience
- ◆ Payroll
- Professional Presentations

Employment History _

VISION TECHNICAL MOLDING - MANCHESTER, CT - PLANNER/SCHEDULER

2010

- Managed major accounts including Corning, Becton-Dickenson, Covidien and NP Medical
- Purchased department supplies and equipment including tool room components, metrology equipment and clean room required items
- Planned press operations based upon new work orders received
- Processed work orders and maintained sales order processing within database tracking system
- ◆ Handled supply order tracking with outside vendors
- Worked with multiple departments to ensure customer orders are processed and delivered on time
- ◆ Involved in Lean Manufacturing training

ROCKBESTOS SURPRENANT CABLE CORP - E. GRANBY, CT - PLANNER/SCHEDULER 2008-2009

- Processed MTO customer orders by planning all shop order operations
- ♦ Maintained and upheld all crib stock tracking reports
- ◆ Printed all planned operations and delivered to appropriate personnel
- ◆ Managed Fire Safety Cell scrap ticket program
- ♦ Assisted both Cell Manager and Materials Manager with special projects

ROCKBESTOS SURPRENANT CABLE CORP - E. GRANBY, CT - EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT 2004-2008

- Maintained current order file system for Sales staff of ten both physically and electronically
- Tracked all manufacturing orders from order entry through production and out to the customer
- Managed extensive workload of projects from sales, marketing and engineering departments
- Acted as backup to staff with regards to order entry, daily bookings and claims
- ◆ Appointed to Sales Department 5s Audit Team

HAMILTON SUNDSTRAND (contract position) - WINDSOR LOCKS, CT - EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT 2004

- Entered vendors for multiple California and Singapore database loads
- Maintained timeline for system entry to coincide with database testing
- Provided executive support to Senior Financial Analysts, General Manager and Vice President of Finance
- ◆ Completed projects and presentations for Finance Department personnel accurately and on time

Employment History (cont.)	
MANPOWER FINANCIAL OPERATIONS (contract position) - ENFIELD, CT – PAYROLL A REPRESENTATIVE/EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT	CCOUNT 2003-2004
 Ensured timely and accurate completion of time slips and expense reimbursement processing temporary employees and sub-contractors 	g for 750+
 Recorded and documented federal and local government agencies requests to investigate empirinformation 	ployment and wage
 Conducted audit research for the home office, field offices and customers 	
Proactively maintained departmental priorities as characteristics of tasks changed	
 Single point of contact for twelve field offices within the Northeast region 	
ACE/ESIS INSURANCE – WINDSOR, CT – EXECUTIVE ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT	1999-2002
 Created interactive PowerPoint presentations and proposals for existing and prospective client 	nts
 Served as liaison between Company representatives and Regional Managers 	
 Conducted extensive internet research and established priorities, tasks and work-flow to mee Delivered on-site Microsoft Office training to staff in Windsor, CT office and Buffalo, NY o 	
Education	
SAINT JOSEPH COLLEGE – WEST HARTFORD, CT	
Bachelor of Science	
References	

References are available upon request.